Fictional Testing Center records
TS-EAS
The Fictional Testing Center records
1968-1999
The Fictional Testing Center
002
1.5 linear feet
TS-EAS Repository
Custodial History
These materials were transferred to the TS-EAS Repository in December 1999 as Dr. Martin ended his tenure as dirctor of the Fictional Testing Center.
Restrictions on Access
Unrestricted access.
Scope and Contents
Records relating to the Fictional Testing Center from 1969-1999, including annual reports, correspondence, photographs, and subject files related to programming and testing protocols developed by the Center.
Container List
- Annual reports, 1968-1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Annual reports, 1976-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Annual reports, 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Annual reports, 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1968-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1976-1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Photographs, 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Seminar: "Learning about the Universe," Caldwell 99, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Seminar: "Getting your Geography Right for a Better Story," 1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Subject file: grants (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Subject file: testing experiments, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Subject file: outcome improvement suggestions (Box 3, Folder 3)